https://naturistsociety.com/the-naturist-society-foundations-privacy-policy/

Skip to content
The Naturist Society Foundation's Privacy Statement
The Naturist Society Foundation believes that your privacy is
important. We are committed to preserving your privacy and will not
under any circumstances sell, trade, or rent any personal information
that is collected from you.
Merchandise orders and information are shipped in a plain envelope labeled with the “N” logo and our return address. The words “nude” and “naturist” do not appear in the return address.
Information collected by The Naturist Society Foundation is stored in
a secure location; access is limited to the TNSF board and staff.
Information provided to us is used solely to identify and serve the
member/customer.
Personal information, including name, address, phone number, and
credit card number, is encrypted using secure software. This ensures
that all information passed through the Internet can only be read by our
system.
Website Security Information
Personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in
the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user
agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a
hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using
it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here:
https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your
profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
Visitors to the
website can download and extract any location data from images on the
website.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your
name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your
convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when
you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos,
images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in
the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed
additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that
embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded
content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
NO ONE
How long we retain your data
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the
personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can
see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they
cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and
edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can
request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about
you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request
that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include
any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security
purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Share this:TweetEmailLike this:Like Loading...
Send to Email Address
Your Name
Your Email Address
Cancel
Post was not sent - check your email addresses!
Email check failed, please try again
Sorry, your blog cannot share posts by email.
%d bloggers like this:
